Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:0 SBat:7.4V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:1 SBat:7.4V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:1 SBat:7.3V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:1 SBat:7.3V GBat:10.7V Delay:31ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:2 SBat:7.3V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:2 SBat:7.2V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:2 SBat:7.2V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:2 SBat:7.1V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:3 SBat:7.1V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:3 SBat:7.1V GBat:10.7V Delay:31ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:3 SBat:7.1V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:3 SBat:7.0V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:4 SBat:7.0V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:4 SBat:7.0V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:4 SBat:7.0V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:4 SBat:6.9V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:4 SBat:6.9V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:5 SBat:6.9V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:5 SBat:6.9V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:5 SBat:6.9V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:5 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:5 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.7V Delay:31ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:4m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:6 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:2m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:6 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.7V Delay:31ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:2m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:6 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:4m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:7 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:2m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:7 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:4m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:7 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:4m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:7 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:2m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:7 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:5m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:7 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:4m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:8 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:5m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:8 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:7m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:8 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:5m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:8 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:5m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:8 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:7m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:9 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:7m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:9 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.6V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:8m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:9 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:8m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:9 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.6V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:8m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:9 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.6V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:7m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:10 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.6V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:8m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:10 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.6V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:10m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:10 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.6V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:8m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:10 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.6V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:8m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:10 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.6V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:7m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:10 SBat:6.5V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:7m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:11 SBat:6.5V GBat:10.6V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:8m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:11 SBat:6.5V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:7m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:11 SBat:6.5V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:5m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:11 SBat:6.5V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:4m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:12 SBat:6.5V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:2m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:12 SBat:6.5V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:2m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:12 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.7V Delay:34ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:12 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.7V Delay:32ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:13 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:13 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.6V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:13 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.7V Delay:31ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:13 SBat:6.6V GBat:10.6V Delay:31ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:1m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:13 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.6V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:13 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.7V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:14 SBat:6.7V GBat:10.6V Delay:33ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m
Signal:4 CH:3 FlightTime:0 SBat:6.8V GBat:10.6V Delay:31ms Bitrate:25.0Mbps Distance:0m